Guide to the Robert M. Palmer papers, 1935-2012.
Palmer, Robert M. papers
- Series VII. Sound Recordings
  - Subseries VIIa. Analog Audio Tapes
    - Mother's Day Tape, 1995; TR-9182 (Box 39)
    - Eastman Concert, TR-9183 (Box 39)
    - Concerto for Wind Quintet and String Orchestra- Walter Ross, TR-9184 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Universtiy Orchestra, Symphony No. 1, TR-9185 (Box 39)
    - Carmina Amoris, TR-9186 (Box 39)
    - Four Hand Piano Sonata, Quintet for Woodwinds, TR-9187 (Box 39)
    - Ray Salvatore recital, Sonata No. 3, TR-9188 (Box 39)
    - Of Night and the Sea- part 1, incomplete, TR-9189 (Box 39)
    - Viola Sonata, TR-9190 (Box 39)
    - Sonata for Piano Four Hands, TR-9191 (Box 39)
    - Viola Sonata, TR-9192 (Box 39)
    - String Quartet No. 3, TR-9193 (Box 39)
    - Memorial Music, Robert Palmer, 3 copies, TR-9194-9196 (Box 39)
    - Second Sonata for Cello and Piano, 4 copies, TR-9197-9200 (Box 39)
    - Toccata Ostinato (1944), TR-9201 (Box 39)
    - Quartet No. 5, two copies, TR-9202-9203 (Box 39)
    - Five piano pieces, Emperor Waltz, TR-9204 (Box 39)
    - Palmer Sonata, trumpet part, TR-9205 (Box 39)
    - Piano Quartet No. 1, two copies, TR-9206-9207 (Box 39)
    - Symphony No. 2, two copies, TR-9208-9209 (Box 39)
    - Quintet for A-Clarinet, String Trio and Piano, TR-9210-9211 (Box 39)
    - Quartet for Piano and Strings, four copies, TR-9212-9215 (Box 39)
    - Robert Palmer 75th Birthday Retrospective Concert, 1990-06-02; TR-17110 (Box 39)
    - Palmer - Trumpet Sonata, Stravinski - Rites - Piano Duet, TR-17111 (Box 39)
    - Palmer Transition Toccata Ostinato, TR-17112 (Box 39)
  - Subseries VIIb. Digital Audio Tapes
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, March 3, 1990; TR-9216 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Musica Nova: conductor Edward Murray, Tape 1, April 7, 1990; TR-9217 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Musica Nova: conductor Edward Murray, Tape 2, April 7, 1990; TR-9218 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, April 28, 1990; TR-9219 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, March 2, 1991; TR-9220 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Musica Nova, April 20, 1991; TR-9221 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, May 4, 1991; TR-9222 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, November 23, 1991; TR-9223 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Musica Nova, April 12, 1992; TR-9224 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, May 2, 1992; TR-9227 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, November 20, 1993; TR-9225 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, March 5, 1994; TR-9226 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, May 7, 1994; TR-9228 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, October 1, 1994; TR-9229 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, November 20, 1994; TR-9230 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, May 6, 1995; TR-9231 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, TR-9232 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, Mahler Symphony, TR-9233 (Box 39)
  - Subseries VIIc. Reel-to-reel Audio Tapes
    - Abe Lincoln March at Midnight, TR-9234 (Box 39)
    - Italian for Modern Living, TR-9235 (Box 39)
    - Italian for Modern Living, TR-9236 (Box 39)
    - Italian for Modern Living, TR-9237 (Box 39)
    - Dances for Small Spaces, Divertimento for Woodwind Quintet, TR-9238 (Box 39)
    - Declaration for Cello and Piano, Sonata, 1967, 1971; TR-9239 (Box 39)
    - Transitions, TR-9240 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Orchestra, April 29, 1989; TR-9241 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Musica Nova, April 1, 1989; TR-9242 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, TR-9243 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, TR-9244 (Box 39)
    - L'Enfance du Christ, TR-9245 (Box 39)
    - L'Enfance du Christ, TR-9246 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, November 23, 1985; TR-9247 (Box 39)
    - Cornell Symphony Orchestra, December 8, 1979; TR-9248 (Box 39)
  - Subseries VIId. CDs
    - Nabuchodonosor, CD-1638 (Box 39)
    - Palmer 75th Birthday Concert, June 2, 1990; CD-1639 (Box 39)
    - Music in the American Grain, 1991; CD-1640 (Box 39)
  - Subseries VIIe. Oral History Interviews
    - Interviews with friends/colleagues of Robert Palmer: Malcolm Lewis, James Webster, and Steven Stucky, February-March 2012; CD-1641 (Box 39)